Shree Ram Bansal

Full Stack Developer

Near Gau Ghat , Badi Basti , Pushkar 305022 <u>shreerambanasal@gmail.com</u> , (+91) 9461214514 <u>WWW</u> , <u>Github</u> , <u>Facebook</u> , <u>Linkedin</u>

Profile

I am a philomath currently pursuing my under graduation in computer science and engineering. I have prior hands-on experience in Full stack Development using HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, JAVA, JSP, JDBC, PHP. I am a self learner. I never know what's the next thing I would be interested in but what I do know is that I would totally give my best for it. Currently I am focused on learning node.js, anguler js, react etc.

Work Experience

ASME E-Fest Music Festival Website - Front end Developer

Jan 2017 - Mar 2017

Contribute in developing website for ASME Efest 2017.

Desportivos 2017 Website - Front End Developer

Dec 2016 - Jan 2017

Contributor in developing website for Desportivos , annual Sports festival of LNMIIT . peoples can see and get info about college , sports fest and can register through this website.

Online Lecture hall booking portal - Front End Developer

Dec 2016 - Jan 2017

Works as front end developer in Online Lecture hall booking portal for LNMIIT. Peoples can book their desired Lecture hall by this portal.

Student Gymkhana Website - Front End Developer

Jun 2016 - Oct 2016

Part of a team in developing Website for student gymkhana.

Education

Taramani Senior Secondary School , Pushkar - Secondary

2010 - 2012

Got 78.20% in Class X (RBSE Board).

Govt. Senior Secondary School, Pushkar - Senior Secondary

2012 - 2014

Got 70.20% in Class XII (RBSE Board).

The LNM Institute of Information Technology, Jaipur -

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech), Computer Science & Engineering

2015 - 2019(Expected)

Current CGPA - 7.34.

Skills

Technical - HTML5, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, BOOTSTRAP, JAVA, JSP, SQL.

Position of Responsibility

Coordinator

Current

Coordinator of Nirog Club In Institute.

Mentor

Current

Mentor of PHOENIX Robotics club in Institute.

Teaching Assistant

Jan 2017 - May 2017

Worked as Teaching Assistant in UG physics lab.

Coordinator

Jan 2017

Was a Coordinator of Robowar event in Tech-fest Plinth'17.

Sub Coordinator

July 2016 - May 2017

Was a Sub Coordinator of Nirog Club In Institute.

Active Member

July 2016 - May 2017

Was an Active Member of PHOENIX club (Robotics) In Institute.

Volunteer

Sep 2016

Volunteer in ICACCI Conference 2016.

Volunteer

Oct 2016

Volunteer in AISYWC conference 2016.